Midtown Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Administrative Correspondence, 1927-1989, undated, Series 1:; (51 linear ft.)
  - General Correspondence, 1932-1983, undated, 1.1:
    - Moran, William F. (see also: Insurance), 1960-1977 (Reel 5355, Frame 1105-1375)
    - MORE-MORI (Reel 5355, Frame 1376-1445)
    - MORRE-MORSE, E. (Reel 5355, Frame 1446-1475)
    - Morse Gallery (Rollins College), 1951-1964 (Reel 5355, Frame 1476-1512)
    - MORSE, R.-MOSL (Reel 5355, Frame 1516-1555)
    - MOSL, cont'd.-MOUNT HE... (Reel 5356, Frame 5-57)
    - Mount Holyoke College, 1941-1974 (Reel 5356, Frame 58-139)
    - MOUNT S...-MUND (Reel 5356, Frame 140-202)
    - Municipal Art Committee, 1934-1938 (Reel 5356, Frame 203-246)
    - Municipal Art Society, 1963-1981 (Reel 5356, Frame 247-288)
    - MUNICIPAL B...-MUNSI (Reel 5356, Frame 289-302)
    - Munson Gallery, 1944, 1972-1978, undated (Reel 5356, Frame 303-355)
    - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1941-1983 (Reel 5356, Frame 356-952)
    - MURC-MUSEUM OF ART, ARIZONA... (Reel 5356, Frame 953-1029)
    - Museum of Art, Ogunquit, Maine, 1953-1972 (Reel 5356, Frame 1030-1120)
    - Museum of Fine Arts [Boston], 1935-1984 (Reel 5356, Frame 1121-1295)
    - Museum of Fine Arts [Houston], 1934-1958 (Reel 5356, Frame 1296-1363)
    - MUSEUM OF FINE ARTS [Springfield, Mass.]-MUSEUM OF MODERN ART [Milan] (Reel 5356, Frame 1364-1368)
    - Museum of Modern Art [New York], 1935-1947 (Reel 5356, Frame 1369-1561)
    - Museum of Modern Art [New York], cont., 1947-1973 (Reel 5357, Frame 5-299)
    - Museum of Modern Art [Sao Paulo], 1951 (Reel 5357, Frame 300-311)
    - Museum of Modern Art Gallery of Washington, D.C., 1937-1939 (Reel 5357, Frame 312-333)
    - Museum of New Mexico, 1965 (Reel 5357, Frame 334-336)
    - MUSEUM OF THE C...-MUSEUM OF THE N... (Reel 5357, Frame 337-367)
    - MUSEUMS-MY (Reel 5357, Frame 368-396)
    - NAA-NASHE (Reel 5357, Frame 397-455)
    - Nashville Museum of Art, 1945-1949 (Reel 5357, Frame 456-496)
    - NASS-NATION (Reel 5357, Frame 497-539)
    - National Academy of Design, 1940-1984, undated (Reel 5357, Frame 540-997)
    - NATIONAL AI...-NATIONAL ART E... (Reel 5357, Frame 998-1009)
    - National Art Museum of Sport, Inc., 1963-1979, undated (Reel 5357, Frame 1010-1469)
    - National Art Week, 1940-1942 (Reel 5357, Frame 1470-1547)
    - National Arts and Antiques Festival, 1965 (Reel 5358, Frame 5-15)
    - National Arts Club, 1940-1980 (Reel 5358, Frame 16-68)
    - NATIONAL AS...-NATIONAL BA.. (Reel 5358, Frame 69-88)
    - National Broadcasting Co. [NBC], 1947-1975 (Reel 5358, Frame 89-215)
    - NATIONAL CA.-NATIONAL COUNCIL ON A... (Reel 5358, Frame 216-240)
    - National Council of Jewish Women, Brooklyn Section. 1961-1966 (Reel 5358, Frame 256-261)
    - National Council of Jewish Women, Essex Co. [N.J.] Section (see also: Essex Co. [N.J.] Section, National Council of Jewish Women), 1955-1981 (Reel 5358, Frame 262-423)
    - National Council of Jewish Women, New York Section, 1960 (Reel 5358, Frame 424-430)
    - National Council of Jewish Women, N. Essex [N.J.] Section (Reel 5358, Frame 431-447)
    - National Council of Women of the United States, Inc., 1960-1975 (Reel 5358, Frame 448-465)
    - NATIONAL CY...-NATIONAL F... (Reel 5358, Frame 466-480)
    - National Institute of Arts and Letters (see: American Academy and National Institute of Arts and Letters) (Reel 5358)
    - NATIONAL G...-NATIONAL N... (Reel 5358, Frame 481-533)
    - National Portrait Gallery (see also: Smithsonian Institution), 1971-1979 (Reel 5358, Frame 534-609)
    - NATIONAL POW...-NAVAJ (Reel 5358, Frame 610-655)
    - Navas, Mrs. Rafael, 1939-1956 (Reel 5358, Frame 656-687)
    - NAZ-NEBRASKA A... (Reel 5358, Frame 688-692)
    - NBC (see: National Broadcasting Co.) (Reel 5358)
    - Nebraska State Teachers College, 1958-1959 (Reel 5358, Frame 1076-1087)
    - Nebraska, University of, 1937-1974, undated (Reel 5358, Frame 693-1075)
    - NEE-NELSON, O. (Reel 5358, Frame 1088-1121)
    - Nelson, William Rockhill, Gallery of Art, 1934-1969 (Reel 5358, Frame 1122-1423)
    - NEM-NEV (Reel 5358, Frame 1424-1505)
    - NEW A... (Reel 5358, Frame 1506-1527)
    - New Britain Institute, 1940-1942 (Reel 5358, Frame 1528-1549)
    - New Britain Institute, cont., 1942-1976 (Reel 5359, Frame 5-108)
    - NEW BRU...-NEW HAMPSHIRE (Reel 5359, Frame 109-146)
    - New Jersey State Museum, 1968-1972 (Reel 5359, Frame 147-311)
    - NEW L...-NEW YORK A... (Reel 5359, Frame 312-393)
    - New York City Board of Education (see also: Board of Education of New York City), 1930-1973 (Reel 5359, Frame 394-478)
    - NEW YORK CITY C...-NEW YORK CITY W... (Reel 5359, Frame 479-495)
    - New York Cultural Center, 1969-1973 (Reel 5359, Frame 496-526)
    - NEW YORK D...-NEW YORK F... (Reel 5359, Frame 527-533)
    - New York Graphic Society, 1949-1979 (Reel 5359, Frame 534-592)
    - New York Herald Tribune, 1938-1964 (Reel 5359, Frame 593-693)
    - NEW YORK HI...-NEW YORK I... (Reel 5359, Frame 694-701)
    - New York Journal American, 1957-1965 (Reel 5359, Frame 702-715)
    - NEW YORK M...-NEW YORK S... (Reel 5359, Frame 716-791)
    - New York Telephone Co., 1933-1978 (Reel 5359, Frame 792-827)
    - New York Times, 1947-1983 (Reel 5359, Frame 828-1041)
    - NEW YORK TO...-NEW YORK WORLD... (Reel 5359, Frame 1042-1081)
    - New York World's Fair, 1938-1939, undated (Reel 5359, Frame 1082-1267)
    - New York World's Fair Corp., 1963-1964 (Reel 5359, Frame 1268-1279)
    - New Yorker, 1943-1975 (Reel 5359, Frame 1280-1301)
    - Newark Museum, 1944-1977 (Reel 5359, Frame 1302-1455)
    - NEWB-NEX (Reel 5359, Frame 1302-1304)
    - Newell-Emmet, 1945-1947 (Reel 5359, Frame 1305-1320)
    - NEWH-NEX (Reel 5359, Frame 1321-1383)
    - Newport [R.I.] Art Association (see: Art Association of Newport [R.I.]) (Reel 5359)
    - NIC (Reel 5359, Frame 1456-1533)
    - NIE-NIK (Reel 5359, Frame 1534-1554)
    - NIL-NOL (Reel 5360, Frame 5-39)
    - Nopper, Lewis (Reel 5360, Frame 40-75)
    - NORC (Reel 5360, Frame 76-81)
    - Nordness Gallery, 1960-1968 (Reel 5360, Frame 82-104)
    - Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences, 1939-1971 (Reel 5360, Frame 105-211)
    - NORM-NORTE (Reel 5360, Frame 212-219)
    - NORTH A...-NORTH CAROLINA N... (Reel 5360, Frame 220-261)
    - North Carolina State Art Society, 1945-1950 (Reel 5360, Frame 262-290)
    - NORTH CAROLINA STATE C...- NORTH CAROLINA STATE D... (Reel 5360, Frame 291-302)
    - North Carolina, University of, 1943-1947 (Reel 5360, Frame 303-347)
    - NORTH CAROLINA W...-NORTH SHORE A... (Reel 5360, Frame 348-471)
    - North Shore Child Guidance Association, 1958-1975 (Reel 5360, Frame 372-400)
    - NORTH SHORE U...-NORTHEAST (Reel 5360, Frame 401-425)
    - NORTHERN (Reel 5360, Frame 426-462)
    - Northfield School, 1946-1967 (Reel 5360, Frame 463-498)
    - NORTHS-NORTON, E. (Reel 5360, Frame 499-511)
    - Norton Gallery and School of Art (Palm Beach Art League), 1946-1967 (Reel 5360, Frame 512-622)
    - NORW-NOT (Reel 5360, Frame 623-646)
    - Noun, Louise, 1962-1983 (Reel 5360, Frame 647-685)
    - NOV-NUN (Reel 5360, Frame 686-708)
    - OA (Reel 5360, Frame 709-736)
    - Oberlin College (Allen Memorial Museum), 1938-1949 (Reel 5360, Frame 737-825)
    - OBG-OBR (Reel 5360, Frame 826-836)
    - Oceanic Investing Corp., 1932-1935 (Reel 5360, Frame 837-865)
    - OCH-OCT (Reel 5360, Frame 866-872)
    - Oehlert, Benjamin H., 1957-1975 (Reel 5360, Frame 873-1064)
    - OEHSC-OK (Reel 5360, Frame 1067-1079)
    - Ogunquit, Maine, Museum of Art (see: Museum of Art, Ogunquit, Maine) (Reel 5360)
    - Oklahoma Art Center, 1942-1975 (Reel 5360, Frame 1177-1292)
    - OKLAHOMA C...-OM (Reel 5360, Frame 1293-1359)
    - Once Upon a Time Press (see also: Stansbury, Henry H.), 1948-1981 (Reel 5360, Frame 1360-1399)
    - Onandoga Silk Co., 1946-1955 (Reel 5360, Frame 1433-1468)
    - ONE-ORED (Reel 5360, Frame 1400-1432)
    - Orecchia, Signora Emilia (see: Balis, Ann) (Reel 5360)
    - Oregon, University of, 1949-1950 (Reel 5360, Frame 1469-1497)
    - ORI-OTTI. (Reel 5360, Frame 1498-1556)
    - OU-OWEN, B. (Reel 5361, Frame 5-25)
    - Owen Gallery, Inc., 1968-1975 (Reel 5361, Frame 26; 28-225)
    - OWEN, V.-PAG (Reel 5361, Frame 27; 226-277)
    - Pahlmann, William, 1952-1974, undated (Reel 5361, Frame 278-404)
    - PAI (Reel 5361, Frame 405-439)
    - PAL (Reel 5361, Frame 440-521)
    - Palm Beach Art League (see: Norton Gallery and School of Art) (Reel 5361)
    - PAN-PAP (Reel 5361, Frame 522-553)
    - PARA-PARI (Reel 5361, Frame 554-614)
    - Park Ave. Social Review (Park Ave. Assn.), 1938-1940 (Reel 5361, Frame 615-649)
    - PARK AVE. T...-PARKS (Reel 5361, Frame 650-714)
    - Parliament Galleries, 1969-1973 (Reel 5361, Frame 715-739)
    - PARM (Reel 5361, Frame 740-742)
    - Parnes, Sidmore, 1956-1978, undated (Reel 5361, Frame 743-810)
    - PARR (Reel 5361, Frame 811-813)
    - Parrish Art Museum, 1946-1964 (Reel 5361, Frame 860-910)
    - Parrish Art Museum, cont., 1965 [filed as Southampton Parrish Art Museum] (Reel 5368, Frame 357)
    - PARRISH B...-PART (Reel 5361, Frame 814-859)
    - Pasadena Art Institute, 1946-1964 (Reel 5361, Frame 911-957)
    - PAT (Reel 5361, Frame 958-1010)
    - PAU-PAY (Reel 5361, Frame 1011-1049)
    - PEA-PEL (Reel 5361, Frame 1050-1133)
    - Pen and Palette, 1949 (Reel 5361, Frame 1134-1148)
    - PENC-PENNE (Reel 5361, Frame 1149-1181)
    - Penney, Charles R., 1968-1976 (Reel 5361, Frame 1182-1208)
    - PENNO-PEPP (Reel 5362, Frame 398-412)
    - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1933-1948 (Reel 5361, Frame 1209-1502)
    - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, cont., 1949-1975 (Reel 5362, Frame 5-301)
    - Pennsylvania C...-Pennsylvania U... (Reel 5362, Frame 302-397)
    - Pepsi Cola, 1957-1977 (Reel 5362, Frame 413-422)
    - Pepsi Cola's Annual Art Competition, "Paintings of the Year," 1945-1949 (Reel 5362, Frame 423-498)
    - PERC-PERLM (Reel 5362, Frame 499-538)
    - Perls Galleries, 1970 (Reel 5362, Frame 539-551)
    - PERLY-PERS (Reel 5362, Frame 552-568)
    - Perutz, George J., 1957-1972 (Reel 5362, Frame 569-665)
    - Petcavage, Albert, 1960-1976 (Reel 5362, Frame 666-695)
    - PETE-PHE (Reel 5362, Frame 696-729)
    - Phibbs Advertising Co., 1946-1947 (Reel 5362, Frame 730-747)
    - Philadelphia Art Alliance, 1934-1977 (Reel 5362, Frame 748-1171)
    - PHILADELPHIA C...-PHILADELPHIA I... (Reel 5362, Frame 1172-1195)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1936-1974 (Reel 5362, Frame 1196-1272)
    - Philadelphia Record, 1936 (Reel 5362, Frame 1273-1274)
    - Philadelphia Water Color Club, 1964-1974 (Reel 5362, Frame 1275-1308)
    - Philbrook Art Center, 1941-1973 (Reel 5362, Frame 1309-1402)
    - PHILIP-PHILIPS (Reel 5362, Frame 1403-1410)
    - Philips Academy (see: Addison Gallery) (Reel 5362)
    - Phillips Collection, 1937-1975 (Reel 5362, Frame 1411-1451)
    - PHILLIPS, E.-PHIP (Reel 5362, Frame 1452-1474)
    - Phoenix Art Museum, 1964-1977 (Reel 5362, Frame 1475-1499)
    - PHOT-PHY (Reel 5362, Frame 1500-1507)
    - Picarello, Frank, 1953-1977 (Reel 5362, Frame 1508-1585)
    - PICC-PICK (Reel 5363, Frame 5-23)
    - Pictorial Forum, 1938 (Reel 5363, Frame 24-47)
    - Pictures on Exhibit, 1947-1966 (Reel 5363, Frame 48-66)
    - PID-PITM (Reel 5363, Frame 67-101)
    - Pittsburgh Arts and Crafts Center, 1948-1952 (Reel 5363, Frame 102-131)
    - PITTSBURGH P...-PL (Reel 5363, Frame 132-168)
    - POD-POL (Reel 5363, Frame 169-239)
    - PON-PORTER, CH... (Reel 5363, Frame 240-293)
    - Porter, Cole, 1937-1955 (Reel 5363, Frame 294-361)
    - PORTER, E.-PORTLAND CO. (Reel 5363, Frame 362-381)
    - Portland [Maine] Museum of Art, 1978 (Reel 5363, Frame 382-383)
    - Portland [Maine] Museum of Art, cont., 1978 (Reel 5363, Frame 440-469)
    - Portland [Maine] Society of Art, 1937-1954 (Reel 5363, Frame 384-413)
    - Portland [Oregon] Art Association, 1939-1941 (Reel 5363, Frame 414-419)
    - Portland [Oregon] Art Museum, 1937-1980 (Reel 5363, Frame 420-437)
    - PORTLAND [Oregon], U...-PORTS (Reel 5363, Frame 470-501)
    - POS-POZ (Reel 5363, Frame 502-538)
    - PRA (Reel 5363, Frame 539-564)
    - PRE (Reel 5363, Frame 565-600)
    - PRIC-PRIN (Reel 5363, Frame 601-637)
    - Prior, Harris K. (Reel 5363, Frame 639-738)
    - PRIS (Reel 5363, Frame 638)
    - PRO (Reel 5363, Frame 739-784)
    - PRU (Reel 5363, Frame 785-800)
    - PUB-PURC (Reel 5363, Frame 801-847)
    - Purdue University, 1947-1981 (Reel 5363, Frame 848-918)
    - PURDY-Q (Reel 5363, Frame 919-964)
    - RAB-RADIC (Reel 5363, Frame 965-1007)
    - Radio Broadcasts, 1932-1938, undated (Reel 5363, Frame 1008-1203)
    - RADIO C...-RAI (Reel 5363, Frame 1204-1266)
    - RAK-RAND (Reel 5363, Frame 1267-1296)
    - Randolph Macon Woman's College, 1946-1982 (Reel 5363, Frame 1297-1372)
    - RANDOM-RAV (Reel 5363, Frame 1373-1436)
    - RAY (Reel 5363, Frame 1437-1515)
    - Raymond & Raymond, Inc., 1945-1959 (Reel 5363, Frame 1516-1571)
    - Raymond & Wakley (Roland Store, Bloomington, Ill.), 1942-1945 (Reel 5364, Frame 5-59)
    - RAYN-READ (Reel 5364, Frame 60-70)
    - Reader's Digest, 1947-1966 (Reel 5364, Frame 71-101)
    - READI-RED (Reel 5364, Frame 102-168)
    - REE-REF (Reel 5364, Frame 169-203)
    - Regenstein, Louis, 1961-1977 (Reel 5364, Frame 204-250)
    - REGI-REI (Reel 5364, Frame 251-307)
    - REM-REP (Reel 5364, Frame 308-358)
    - RES (Reel 5364, Frame 359-408)
    - Rhode Island School of Design, 1936-1983 (Reel 5364, Frame 409-485)
    - RIC (Reel 5364, Frame 486-549)
    - Richmond [Ind.] Art Association (see: Art Association of Richmond [Ind.]) (Reel 5364)
    - RID-RING (Reel 5364, Frame 550-584)
    - Ringling Museum of Art, 1948-1983 (Reel 5364, Frame 585-615)
    - RIO-RIX (Reel 5364, Frame 616-659)
    - ROA-ROBINSON, MARK (Reel 5364, Frame 660-749)
    - Robinson, Mary Turlay, 1939-1965, undated (Reel 5364, Frame 750-803)
    - ROBINSON, S.-ROBY (Reel 5364, Frame 804-851)
    - Rochester [Minn.] Art Gallery, 1947-1950 (Reel 5364, Frame 852-884)
    - Rochester [N.Y.] Institute of Technology (Reel 5364, Frame 885-889)
    - Rochester [N.Y.] Memorial Art Gallery, 1934-1982 (Reel 5364, Frame 890-1236)
    - ROCHESTER COUNTY [N.Y.] P...-ROCK (Reel 5364, Frame 1237-1240)
    - Rockefeller Home Center, 1941 (Reel 5364, Frame 1241-1298)
    - ROCKEFELLER, J.-ROCKEFELLER, N. (Reel 5364, Frame 1299-1218)
    - Rockford Art Association, 1942-1972 (Reel 5364, Frame 1319-1437)
    - ROCKL-ROE (Reel 5364, Frame 1438-1504)
    - Rogers [Lauren] Museum (see: Lauren Rogers Library and Museum) (Reel 5364)
    - ROG-ROM (Reel 5364, Frame 1505-1560)
    - Roland Store (Bloomigton, Ill.; see: Raymond & Wakley) (Reel 5364)
    - ROO-ROP (Reel 5364, Frame 1561-1583)
    - ROSE, A.-ROSE, S. (Reel 5365, Frame 6-23; 35; 37)
    - Rose, Stanley (see: Stanley Rose Bookstore and Gallery) (Reel 5365)
    - ROSEM-ROSEN (Reel 5365, Frame 34; 36-88)
    - ROSENB-ROSENT (Reel 5365, Frame 89-156)
    - ROSH-ROST (Reel 5365, Frame 157-204)
    - ROSW-ROTH (Reel 5365, Frame 205-227)
    - Rothberg, Howard Perry, 1947-1957, undated (Reel 5365, Frame 228-265)
    - ROTHC-ROWAN, A. (Reel 5365, Frame 267-314)
    - Rowan, Dan, 1967-1970 (Reel 5365, Frame 315-341)
    - Rowan, Edward, 1934-1970 (Reel 5365, Frame 342-520)
    - ROWAN G...-ROY (Reel 5365, Frame 521-529)
    - RUB-RUDD (Reel 5365, Frame 530-588)
    - Ruder & Finn Fine Arts, 1950-1970 (Reel 5365, Frame 590-627)
    - RUDERT (Reel 5365, Frame 628-629)
    - Rudick, Harry, 1943-1970 (Reel 5365, Frame 589; 630-664)
    - RUDK-RUS (Reel 5365, Frame 665-723)
    - Rutgers University, 1960-1982 (Reel 5365, Frame 724-762)
    - RUTH-RY (Reel 5365, Frame 763-840)
    - SAA-SAGE (Reel 5365, Frame 841-880)
    - Saginaw Museum, 1947-1964 (Reel 5365, Frame 881-921)
    - SAGN-SAIB (Reel 5365, Frame 922-925)
    - Saint Augustine Art Association, 1961 (Reel 5365, Frame 926-956)
    - SAINT C...-SAINT J... (Reel 5365, Frame 957-1024)
    - Saint Lawrence College, 1977 (Reel 5365, Frame 1094-1095)
    - Saint Lawrence University, 1952-1976 (Reel 5365, Frame 1025-1093)
    - Saint Louis Artists Guild, 1962 (Reel 5365, Frame 1096-1101)
    - Saint Louis, City Art Museum of (see also: City Art Museum of St. Louis), 1936-1972 (Reel 5365, Frame 1102-1249)
    - SAINT LOUIS G...-SAINT O... (Reel 5365, Frame 1250-1276)
    - St. Paul Art Center, 1966-1968 (Reel 5365, Frame 1277-1287)
    - Saint Paul Gallery and School of Art, 1943-1962 (Reel 5365, Frame 1288-1336)
    - SAINT PETER'S CHURCH-SAINT S... (Reel 5365, Frame 1337-1345)
    - Sakhai, Neil, 1982 (Reel 5365, Frame 1346-1374)
    - Saks Fifth Ave., 1947-1971 (Reel 5365, Frame 1375-1436)
    - SAKS, G.-SALT LAKE A... (Reel 5365, Frame 1437-1459)
    - Salt Lake City, 1938-1950 (Reel 5365, Frame 1460-1487)
    - SALU-SAM (Reel 5365, Frame 1488-1506)
    - San Antonio Art League, 1950-1953 (Reel 5365, Frame 1507-1528)
    - San Antonio Art League, cont., 1953-1959 (Reel 5366, Frame 5-27)
    - San Diego, Fine Arts Gallery of, 1934-1977 (Reel 5366, Frame 28-299)
    - SAN FRANCISCO A...-SAN FRANCISCO C... (Reel 5366, Frame 300-308)
    - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1934-1978 (Reel 5366, Frame 309-385)
    - SAN J...-SAN M... (Reel 5366, Frame 386-397)
    - SAND-SANTA BARBARA B... (Reel 5366, Frame 398-462)
    - Santa Barbara Free Public Library, Faulkner Memorial Art Gallery, 1936-1938 (Reel 5366, Frame 463-491)
    - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1940-1973 (Reel 5366, Frame 492-616)
    - SANTA C...-SANTA F... (Reel 5366, Frame 617-621)
    - SANTI-SAR (Reel 5366, Frame 622-660)
    - SAT-SAY (Reel 5366, Frame 661-696)
    - SCA-SCHA (Reel 5366, Frame 697-778)
    - SCHE-SCHI (Reel 5366, Frame 739-796)
    - SCHL-SCHNA (Reel 5366, Frame 797-814)
    - SCHNEIDER, D.-SCHNEIDER, W. (Reel 5366, Frame 815-844)
    - SCHNEIDERM-SCHOOL A... (Reel 5366, Frame 845-869)
    - School Libraries, 1948-1949, undated (Reel 5366, Frame 870-1026)
    - SCHOOL OF F...-SCHULTE (Reel 5366, Frame 1027-1044)
    - Schultheis, Henry, 1932-1936 (Reel 5366, Frame 1045-1073)
    - SCHULTHES-SCHULZ (Reel 5366, Frame 1074-1089)
    - Schumacher & Co., 1947-1952 (Reel 5366, Frame 1090-1121)
    - SCHUMACK-SCHUY (Reel 5366, Frame 1122-1158)
    - SCHW (Reel 5366, Frame 1159-1234)
    - SCO-SEA H... (Reel 5366, Frame 1235-1304)
    - Sea Isle Hotel, 1950-1952 (Reel 5366, Frame 1305-1354)
    - SEAC-SEARL (Reel 5366, Frame 1355-1362)
    - Sears, Roebuck and Co., 1943-1972 (Reel 5366, Frame 1363-1382)
    - Seattle Art Museum, 1935-1971 (Reel 5366, Frame 1383-1506)
    - SEATTLE P...-SEAY (Reel 5366, Frame 1507-1535)
    - SEC-SELF (Reel 5366, Frame 1536-1556)
    - Selig, Simon, 1965-1976 (Reel 5367, Frame 5-34)
    - SELIGM-SEY (Reel 5367, Frame 35-89)
    - SHA (Reel 5367, Frame 90-210)
    - SHEE-SHER (Reel 5367, Frame 211-275)
    - Shields, Mr. and Mrs. Richard, 1962-1975 (Reel 5367, Frame 276-354)
    - SHIM-SHL (Reel 5367, Frame 355-369)
    - SHO-SHREVE (Reel 5367, Frame 370-412)
    - Shreveport Art Club, 1935-1945 (Reel 5367, Frame 413-429)
    - SHREY-SHULL (Reel 5367, Frame 430-456)
    - Shulman, Herman, 1935-1944 (Reel 5367, Frame 457-490)
    - Shuman, J., 1961 (Reel 5367, Frame 491-492)
    - Shuman, John Rogers, 1942-1963 (Reel 5367, Frame 493-524)
    - SHUMAT-SHUS (Reel 5367, Frame 525-533)
    - Shute, Nell and Ben, 1946-1964, undated (Reel 5367, Frame 534-608)
    - SHUTZ-SHW (Reel 5367, Frame 609-620)
    - SIB-SIK (Reel 5367, Frame 621-665)
    - SILB (Reel 5367, Frame 666-673)
    - Silk Screen Companies, 1941-1943 (Reel 5367, Frame 674-720)
    - SILL-SILVERMA (Reel 5367, Frame 721-751)
    - Silvermine Guild of Artists, Inc., 1946-1947 (Reel 5367, Frame 752-768)
    - SILVERS-SIM (Reel 5367, Frame 769-824)
    - SIN (Reel 5367, Frame 825-869)
    - SIO-SIV (Reel 5367, Frame 870-894)
    - SKI-SKIDE (Reel 5367, Frame 895-918)
    - Skidmore College, 1954-1971 (Reel 5367, Frame 919-952)
    - Skidmore, Owings & Merrill, 1955-1977 (Reel 5367, Frame 953-1015)
    - Skowhegan School of Painting and Sculpture, 1950-1961, undated (Reel 5367, Frame 1016-1066)
    - SLA (Reel 5367, Frame 1067-1107)
    - SLE-SLO (Reel 5367, Frame 1108-1181)
    - SMA-SMITH, C. (Reel 5367, Frame 1182-1227)
    - Smith College, 1934-1976 (Reel 5367, Frame 1228-1267)
    - SMITH, D.-SMITH, G. (Reel 5367, Frame 1268-1289)
    - Smith, George Vincent Walter, Art Museum, 1942-1971, undated (Reel 5367, Frame 1290-1343)
    - SMITH, GERTRUDE-SMITHE (Reel 5367, Frame 1344-1437)
    - Smithsonian Institution (see also: National Portrait Gallery), 1945- 1981 (Reel 5367, Frame 1438-1566)
    - SMITHT-SNEE (Reel 5368, Frame 5-46)
    - SNEL-SNY (Reel 5368, Frame 47-60)
    - SOB-SOCIETY OF I... (Reel 5368, Frame 61-86)
    - Society of the Four Arts, 1940-1973 (Reel 5368, Frame 87-188)
    - SOK-SOUR (Reel 5368, Frame 189-232)
    - South American Exposition (Reel 5368, Frame 233-264)
    - SOUTH AM...-SOUTH B... (Reel 5368, Frame 265-269)
    - South Bend Art Association (see: Art Center, South Bend) (Reel 5368)
    - South County [R.I.] Art Association, 1947-1956 (Reel 5368, Frame 270-287)
    - SOUTH S...-SOUTHERN MI... (Reel 5368, Frame 288-303)
    - Southern Museum Circuit, 1944-1949 (Reel 5368, Frame 305-325)
    - SOUTHERN O...-SOUTHERN S... (Reel 5368, Frame 326-332)
    - Southern Vermont Art Center, 1951-1969 (Reel 5368, Frame 333-354)
    - Southampton College (Reel 5368, Frame 356)
    - Southampton Parrish Museum (see: Parrish Museum) (Reel 5368)
    - SOUTHW (Reel 5368, Frame 358-374)
    - Spa Summer Theater, 1966-1967 (Reel 5368, Frame 375-394)
    - SPAE-SPEE (Reel 5368, Frame 395-424)
    - SPEI-SPER (Reel 5368, Frame 425-480)
    - SPI-SPRINGE (Reel 5368, Frame 482-546)
    - Springfield [Ill.] Art Association, 1939-1954 (Reel 5368, Frame 547-630)
    - Springfield [Mo.] Art Museum, 1945-1978 (Reel 5368, Frame 631-732)
    - SPRINGFIELD [MASS.] A...-SPRINGFIELD [MASS.] D... (Reel 5368, Frame 739-763)
    - Springfield [Mass.] Museum of Fine Arts (see also: Museum of Fine Arts [Springfield, Mass.]), 1933-1976 (Reel 5368, Frame 764-1014)
    - Springfield Union [Mass.], 1967 (Reel 5368, Frame 1015-1016)
    - Springville High School Art Association (Springville Museum of Art), 1946-1974 (Reel 5368, Frame 733-738)
    - Springville High School Art Association (Springville Museum of Art), cont., 1946-1974 (Reel 5368, Frame 1017-1143)
    - SPIVY (Reel 5368, Frame 1144-1145)
    - The Spur, 1936-1938 (Reel 5368, Frame 1146-1167)
    - Squibb & Sons [Gallery], 1948-1970, undated (Reel 5368, Frame 1168-1216)
    - SQUIR (Reel 5368, Frame 1217-1218)
    - STAA-STAL (Reel 5368, Frame 1219-1236)
    - Staman, Mrs. Henry H., 1954-1970, undated (Reel 5368, Frame 1237-1281)
    - STAMAT-STAND (Reel 5368, Frame 1282-1320)
    - Stanford University, 1933-1965 (Reel 5368, Frame 1321-1365)
    - Stanley Rose Bookstore and Gallery, 1936-1940 (Reel 5368, Frame 1366-1399)
    - Stansbury, Henry H., 1948 (Reel 5368, Frame 1403-1558)
    - Stansbury, Henry H., cont. (see also: Once Upon a Time Press), 1948-1951 (Reel 5369, Frame 5-238)
    - STANT-STARL (Reel 5369, Frame 239-261)
    - STARR-STATE A... (Reel 5369, Frame 262-305)
    - State Department (see also: United States Department of State), 1946-1975 (Reel 5369, Frame 306-441)
    - STATE S...-STEA (Reel 5369, Frame 442-495)
    - STEC-STEF (Reel 5369, Frame 496-530)
    - STEI-STENDAHL, E. (Reel 5369, Frame 531-593)
    - Stendahl Galleries, 1938-1942 (Reel 5369, Frame 594-612)
    - STENS-STER (Reel 5369, Frame 613-670)
    - STEV-STEWART, J. (Reel 5369, Frame 671-690)
    - Stewart, Michael, 1962-1978 (Reel 5369, Frame 691-755)
    - Sternberg, Maurice (see: Walton Walk Galleries) (Reel 5369)
    - STI-STONE, E. (Reel 5369, Frame 756-797)
    - Stone, Harry Lewis (see also: Accountants' Reports and Correspondence), 1937-1977 (Reel 5369, Frame 798-861)